<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experience on dannypallotta</title><link>dannyp.github.io/experience/</link><description>Recent content in Experience on dannypallotta</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="dannyp.github.io/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ARTC</title><link>dannyp.github.io/experience/artc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>dannyp.github.io/experience/artc/</guid><description>As the Lead Data Engineer, my role is to establish and mature the overall architecture of the Data Analytics Platform, the frameworks and development practices of the analytics team and to lead the design and delivery of data projects across the enterprise.
Responsibilities Link to heading Lead the solution architecture, design, automation, management, and governance of the data analytics platform Manage the automation and operations of the data loading processes Mentor and coach other technical staff in the application of frameworks and development techniques to enhance technical improvements to the platform Provide production support to solve immediate problems Analyse information requirements of customers and support teams and determine the best technical solutions Collaborate with business and technical partners to understand and evaluate their needs for data from the data analytics Continuous improvement of process, maintain informative and succinct documentation on requirements, processes, architecture designs etc in a shared knowledge base.</description></item><item><title>People's Choice Credit Union</title><link>dannyp.github.io/experience/pccu/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>dannyp.github.io/experience/pccu/</guid><description>Member of the in-house analytics team, worked across the business to deliver a range of analytical and reporting solutions such as interactive insights dashboards, operational and regulatory reporting and data-pipeline performance improvements.
As a Senior Analytics Developer, I had additional responsibility for providing peer review and design guidance within the development team and to influence and add value in the architectural decision making process on occasion.
Key Achievements Link to heading Agile delivery of the EFS suite of reporting to APRA.</description></item><item><title>innodev</title><link>dannyp.github.io/experience/innodev/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>dannyp.github.io/experience/innodev/</guid><description> Notable Projects Link to heading Credit Management Reporting (PCCU): Built a suite of reports to effectively manage credit risk</description></item><item><title>DWS</title><link>dannyp.github.io/experience/dws/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>dannyp.github.io/experience/dws/</guid><description>Notable Projects Link to heading IT Reform Project (ASC and Air Warfare Destroyer Alliance). Migration of business systems from the ASC technology environment to the AWD environment. Detailed Schedule Managment (ASC): Developed a solution to assist supervisors and area managements with their planning and schedule adherance. Isolations Management System (ASC): Developed a system to support the isolation management safety process. BI modernisation and SQL 2017 migration (Wine Australia) supported a project to upgrade the on-prem Business Intelligence platforms and processes.</description></item></channel></rss>